<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Uncategorized &#8211; The Friendship Express</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/uncategorized/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>21-22 March - Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 15:04:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.8.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Make it Better</title>
		<link>/make-it-better/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2015 17:44:59 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[St. Pinkie]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://2015.TheFriendshipExpress.org/?p=725</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Its been about a month and a half since The Friendship Express was first announced to the world and we are thrilled to see great amounts of positive comments from all of you. Thank you all for the kind words! Here at The Friendship Express, we have been super busy getting things together to make [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div align="center"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/vince.png" alt="vince" height="270"></div>
<p>Its been about a month and a half since The Friendship Express was first announced to the world and we are thrilled to see great amounts of positive comments from all of you. Thank you all for the kind words!</p>
<p>Here at The Friendship Express, we have been super busy getting things together to make this convention as awesome as it can possibly get. We have just over a month to go until the big day. In the spirit of making hay while the sun shines, we are thrilled to announce that we are in contact with none other than Vincent Tong, the voice behind Flash Sentry, Donut Joe and Prince Bluebood!</p>
<p>But we need your help. Bringing Vincent down all the way easily triples our convention budget, making that far too expensive for us to afford. However, we were given a counteroffer for the next best thing: A one-hour Skype call with Vincent!</p>
<p>Despite that, this interview will still set us back quite a bit. After putting a lot of money on the table to make The Friendship Express work, we are now turning to you. Yes. YOU &#8211; to give us that one hour window to speak to Vincent at The Friendship Express 2015. The stage is set and the event is a go. Now we are trying to make it better with your help. Check out our <a href="http://pozi.be/tfe">Pozible crowdfunding campaign here</a>. For perks are introducing a whole new ticketing tiers (don&#8217;t worry, basic admission is still free!!) as well as some exclusive limited edition merchandise. The campaign will run from now until the end of the month so let&#8217;s get going!</p>
<p>Together we can do it. Have faith and Believe in Magic!</p>
<p>Love,<br />
St. Pinkie<br />
Convention Chair</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
